{
    "quiz": [
        {
            "question": "How long does the marathon last?",
            "answers": [
                "26.2 miles",
                "26 miles",
                "24 miles"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "26.2 miles"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many players are on the baseball team?",
            "answers": [
                "7",
                "9",
                "10"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country won the 2018 World Cup?",
            "answers": [
                "Switzerland",
                "UK",
                "France"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "France"
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of sport is considered the \"king of sports\"?",
            "answers": [
                "Basketball",
                "Soccer",
                "Hockey"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Soccer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are Canada's two national sports?",
            "answers": [
                "Lacrosse and hockey",
                "American Football",
                "Archery"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Lacrosse and hockey"
        },
        {
            "question": "In what sport would you have a touchdown?",
            "answers": [
                "American Football",
                "Chess",
                "Hockey"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "American Football"
        },
        {
            "question": "In what year did Amir Khan win his Olympic boxing medal?",
            "answers": [
                "2001",
                "2005",
                "2004"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "2004"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the diameter of a basketball hoop in inches?",
            "answers": [
                "16.5 inches",
                "17 inches",
                "18 inches"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "18 inches"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which African country was the first to enter the World Cup?",
            "answers": [
                "Nigeria",
                "Morocco",
                "Egypt"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Egypt"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country hosted the World Athletics Championships for the first time?",
            "answers": [
                "Germany",
                "Helsinki",
                "Norway"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Helsinki"
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is the center of the archery target?",
            "answers": [
                "Yellow",
                "Red",
                "Blue"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Yellow"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the length of the race track in an Olympic-sized pool?",
            "answers": [
                "43 meters",
                "50 meters",
                "65 meters"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "50 meters"
        }
    ]
}